[Music]
t.me/dlmacvin_new
I'm Daniel Cortez I'm a wim HOF method
master instructor health coach strength
t.me/dlmacvin_new
and conditioning and mobility coach and
I was sick for about 15 years and that
t.me/dlmacvin_new
towards the end of my my journey with
chronic illness I found wim
t.me/dlmacvin_new
I saw him I saw wim HOF on a National
Geographic special and I was immediately
t.me/dlmacvin_new
inspired and I ended up training with
women Poland and then I became one of
t.me/dlmacvin_new
his first instructors in the US and wim
and the method helped me to push myself
t.me/dlmacvin_new
to be able to essentially keep myself
afloat until I could find a diagnosis
t.me/dlmacvin_new
and then eventually a cure and that's
what I do now I help people express
t.me/dlmacvin_new
their optimal humanity to be the hero of
their own journey
t.me/dlmacvin_new
[Music]
I'm incredibly grateful to win for for
t.me/dlmacvin_new
showing me this and being an inspiration
providing me this tool that I now use to
t.me/dlmacvin_new
help other people
[Music]
t.me/dlmacvin_new